Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Whittlesey, Walter R., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 342)
  Correspondence with Walter Whittlesey of Washington DC. Whittlesey was an employee of the Library of Congress. His initial contacts with Lilly consisted of answering various questions from the Foster Hall staff. In 1932 he was forced to retire from the Library, but because by that time he was engaged in research for Lilly he was allowed to maintain a desk there and continue his work. After his retirement, Lilly began paying him a monthly allowance. Whittlesey's work was to aid in the systematic coordination of Lilly's collection, verification of facts (copyright, etc.), checking over the reproductions for flaws, assisting E.F. Morneweck in the writing of The Chronicles, mounting such ephemeral material as newspaper clippings, and so on. In short, his high degree of professionalism made him invaluable to the development of the collection. When he died in 1936, his daughter (Katherine Copley), who was already assisting him, remained in Lilly's employment and continued her father's work.
- Wilson, Mary Alice, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  Correspondence with Mary Alice Wilson [see also Johnson, Mary E.] of Indianapolis, IN/ One of two disabled typists employed by the Hall. After the Collection was moved to Pittsburgh she continued to work for Mr. Hodges long distance. Among other tasks she helped to type Mrs. Morneweck's manuscript of The Chronicles.
- Wilson, Judge Samuel W., 1934 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  Correspondence with Judge Samuel W. Wilson of Lexington, KY, a retired judge, Foster fan, and proseltyzer.
- WO WR WU WY, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  Correspondence with Edith A. Wright; Women's Christian Temperance Union; Richard S. Wormser; Florence Woodward; E. Jay Wohlegmuth; Anne H. Woestehoff; University of Wyoming; Ina Woodward; Worcerster Public Library; Woonsocket Harris Institute Library; Henry D. Woertz; C.W. Wynn; Richardson Wright; University of Wyoming; Alexander Woollcott
- Woods, Mrs. Nanno, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Nanno Woods of Los Angeles, CA. A lecturer, she wrote to Foster Hall for information on Foster's life and times.
- XYZ, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  Correspondence with Jay Yohe; Young Men's Christian Association; Zionsville Women's Club; Nona York; Zeta Chapter of Pi Omicron; Zanesville Public Library; Yankton College; John Richcreek Young; Lewis E. Young; Yale University Library; Youngstown Telegram; Yonkers Public Library; Clarence Zollinger
- AA AL, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  Correspondence with Alliance Public Schools; Civic Club of Allegheny County; Roy E. Adams; C.W. Allison; Aberdeen High School; William Agnew; Aberdeen Public Library; Charles Alker; Akron Public Library; Martha Alexander; B.F. Jones Memorial Library Aliquippa; Alhambra City High School; Alfred University; University of Alabama; Alexander Mitchell Library; State of Alabama; Allentown Free Library; Aetna Cabinet Co.; Ada Schools; Arthur Allen; Jane Allison; Velma Alexander; Evelyn Alspach; Allen's Book Store Inc; Josephine Adams; Peggy Althar; Max Aldo; Alpha Latreian Club; Altoona; Mount Union College Alliance OH; Joseph P. Allen Jr.; Elinor Albright; Ben F. Alexander; Akron Public Schools; Albany Public Library; Elliot Allison; Charles Adams; Alfred Allison
- Aeolian Co., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 349)
  Correspondence with the Aeolian Company of NY, NY. Produced three organ rolls of Foster's music, not for sale or distribution, but for use at Foster Hall.
- Aldine Book Co., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  Correspondence with the Aldine Book Company of Brooklyn, NY, one of the Hall's first dealers
- Allgauer, Moriz F.M., 1935 (Box 12, Folder 351)
  Correspondence with Moriz Algauer of Port Chester, NY, a small time bookdealer.
- Alwes Music Shoppe, Gladys, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 352)
  Correspondence with Gladys Alwes Music Shoppe of Indianapolis, IN. Throughout the Hall's existence, Alwes supplied many of the contemporary songbooks containing variations or mentions of Foster's music.
- AM AN AP AQ, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 353)
  Correspondence with W.W. Anderson; Berniece Anstead; Anderson Public Schools; Alexander Andrews; Converse Memorial Library Amherst; Oliver Wendall Holmes Library Andover; Lawrence College Appleton; Carnegie Library Anniston; Ann Arbor Public Library; Angola Carnegie Public Library; Amarillo TX; Paul Anthony; James Andrews; Andover Citizen; Lyman Applegate; Anderson, IN; Iowa State College, Ames; WOI Ames; Anderson Broadcast Corp; Laughlin Memorial Free Library Ambridge; K. Anderson; Oliver Annable; Jones Library Amherst
- Antique Parlors, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 354)
  Correspondence with Antique Parlors of Rutland, VT, a dealer who sold a few pieces to Foster Hall.
- American, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 355)
  Correspondence to and from organizations with American in their title.
- AR AS AT AZ, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 356)
  Correspondence with Board of Education Atlanta, GA; Ashtabula City Schools; F.M. Ayres; Armour Public Library; E.C. Atkins & Company; A. Jefferson Ashburn; Herman Arndt; Atlanta Commercial High School; Auburn Public Library; Nellie Custis School Arlington, VA; Seymour Library Auburn NY; Carnegie Library Atlanta; Melvin E. Atkatz; University of Arizona Library; WPA Athens, OH; Donald B. Arthur; Ashland College; Ollie Ater; Attic Book Shop; Augusta Graded Schools; Art Publication Society; Denelda Archibald; Sondley Reference Library Asheville; Leslie Ashdown; Emily Athens; F.F. Avery; Ashland High School; Attala Broadcasting Corporation; Carrie Arter; Joe E. Avery; Arcane Bookshop; Associated Traffic Club of America; Tioga Point Museum Athens; WCAP Asbury Park; Ara Arnold; H.H. Arnholter; Arcadian Club; G.S. Arnold; Margaret Armon; Carnegie Library Austin, MN; Colony Book Shop Atlanta; O.R. Armostrong; Bertha Armstrong; Atlanta Journal; Knoedler Memorial Library August, KY; Aurora College; Spaulding Memorial Library Athens; Mary E Armington; Associated Music Publishers Inc.
- Archetti, Enzo, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 357)
  Correspondence with Enzo Archetti of Hudson Heights, NJ. Archetti was a record collector who frequently donated Foster-related items to the collection.
- Armstrong, Henry R., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 358)
  Correspondence with Henry Armstrong of Norwich, CT, a minor dealer from whom Foster Hall made a few acquisitions.
- Ayres & Company, L.S., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 359)
  Correspondence with L.S. Ayres & Company of Indianapolis, IN. A purchasing firm which helped Foster Hall purchase books and other materials.
- BAA BAN, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 360)
  Correspondence with Baker & Taylor Co.; Ball State Teacher's College; Nassau Suffolk Little Symphony, Babylon; T.R. Baker; Bangor Public Library; Ann R. Babcock; Gouher College Library Baltimore; Kern County Free Library Bakersfield; Giovanni Baietti; Grace Bacon; Earl Baker; Arthur Ball; Paul Badertscher; Jesse S. Bailey; Badger Broadcasting Co.; Charles C. Baker; Robert John Bialey; William Foster Bailey; David Ross Bailey; Maude Foster Bailay; Mary Irene Bader; Hotel Whitecotton Berkeley; WCAO Baltimore; WBSO Babson Park; D.J. Bach; Baillie's Institution; Baldwin Wallace College; D.H. Badanes; William H. Ball
- Baker, Eunice Jones, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 361)
  Correspondence with Eunice Jones Baker of Acton, IN. Actor was a music teacher who requested songbooks to facilitate teaching Foster's music to her students.
- BAR BAS BAT BAZ, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 362)
  Correspondence with M.E. Barrett; Barkus; Gladys Bartle; Maud Harriman Barrett; Raymond Basso; Robert Y. Barkley; Selma Baum; Dr. C.P. Bartley; Alva Baughman; Thelma Barry; Jack Bartlow; Renee Bartholomew; Charles Bartz Jr.; H.H. Barclay; Margaret Barker; Margaret Bates; Kathryn Barber; James Barnhart; R.P. Barber; Bardstown, KY; James Batman; Book Hunters; Bayonne Free Public Library; Battle Creek Public School Library
- BEA BEC BED BEM, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 363)
  Correspondence with Bellewood IL; John R. Beatty; Bement Township High School; Beloit College; Edna Mary Beam; Ernest Anton Becker; W.A. Beavans; Beaumont TX; Howard Beatty; Catherine Bell; Geneva Beck; Mary Louise Beardsley; Linnie Beeker; Peter Vander Beels; Frederick Bellmar; Margaret Beech; George W. Beakes; Ruth Beall Eugene Beique
- BEN BER BES BEZ, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 364)
  Correspondence with Berea College; Signe Benson; Henry Bentley; Bethlehem Public Library; Baldwin-Wallace College; P.J. Bernard; Charles Beyer; Ray Benner; Robert Benes; Bexley Public Schools; Stanley O. Bezanson; Bethlehem Lutheran Church; Bender's Book Store; C.H. Benjamin; Walter Benjamin; Berkeley Public Library; Berea College; Baldwin-Wallace College
- Birchard & Company, CC, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 365)
  Correspondence with C.C. Birchard & Company of Boston, MA. Music Publishers that Lilly tried to have the school songbook published with, but they dragged their feet and the contract went elsewhere.
- Birge, Edward B., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 366)
  Correspondence with Edward B. Birge of Indianapolis, IN. Edward Birge, a Professor of music at Indiana University, worked with Will Earhart on The Songs of Stephen Foster, a songbook published by University of Pittsburgh Press.
- BI, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 367)
  Correspondence with Mabel Bingler; Birmingham Public Library; Parmly Billings Memorial Library; Universities Bibliothek; Marshall Bidwell; E.B. Bird; Elisha Brown Bird; Glenn Bidwell; L.E. Bird; Margaret Bigley; Warren Biggs; Eugene Bibbins; R.B. Bissett; A.A. Bieber; KFYR Bismarck; George Bickford; Charles Bill; Birmingham Public Library
- BL, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 368)
  Correspondence with Dorothy Black; Dorothy Blackmar; Blue Earth MN; Blue Mountain College; Lillian D. Black; H.L. Bland; Anna Blum; Frieda Blaufuss; Bernice Black; Bladensburg Junior High School; Herman T. Briscoe; Friday Musicale Bloomington; Frieda Blanfuss; B.R. Black; S.W. Blood; R.E.B. Blood; Bloomington City Public Schools; Louis Block; Alice Blews
- BO, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 369)
  Correspondence with Elorie Boll; Roscoe Bogart; Bowling Green State University; Russell Boyd; Boosey Hawkes Belwin Inc.; W.C. Bowyer; Alene Boyenton; Boston University; Boston Library; Boston Athenaeu; Belwin Inc.; Nicholas Boccamaza; Sister Charles Borromeo; Boonville MO; Richard Bolton; Helen Bowen; Hazel Booth; Robert Bock; Florence Booth; Richard Bolton; Ethel Boothby; WMEX Boston; John G. Bowman; Joseph Bowling; Book Clearing House; A.V. Booth; L.G. Bowers; Norman Boehm; Bernice Boeger; Frances Bowman
- Book Lovers Shop, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 370)
  Correspondence with the Book Lovers Shop of Hartford, CT, a book dealer.
- Boston Antique Shop, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 371)
  Correspondence with the Boston Antique Shop of Boston, MA, music dealers that made a few sales to the collection.
- BRA BRE BRI, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 372)
  Correspondence with Sister Serena Branson; H.G. Brannen; Katherine Breid; Ernest Anton Becker; Bridgeport Public Library; Pearl Brown Brands; Captain Taylor Branson; Ruth Brewster; Hosford Brackett; Bremen Public Schools; Robert Bradshaw; Lynn Bridge; WOPI Bristol; Eugenie Brewster; Bradenburg KY; WICC Bridgeport; H.M. Bringhurst; Bradford County Historical Society; Betty Brewer; Grace brewer; E.K. Brasleton; St. Bernard School
- Bragin, Charles, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 373)
  Correspondence with Charles Bragin of Brooklyn, NY. Another collector, he kept a look out for Foster material and donated various items. Mr. Bragin was well-known for his collection of dime store novels.
- Briggs, Morris H., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 374)
  Correspondence with Morris H. Briggs of Chicago, IL, a rare book dealer and one of Lilly's first contacts. Throughout the building of the collection he provided many interesting items, even though his prices were unreasonably high.
- Brooks, Karl L., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 375)
  Correspondence with Karl L. Brooks of Oneonta, NY. Brooks edited a special edition of the State Normal School of Oneonta's publication devoted entirely to the life and work of Stephen Foster. Hodges sent him a large collection of Fosteriana, culled from duplicates in the collection. As the collection was being prepared for Pittsburgh, the Hall staff gave a great deal of material to any interested collectors.
- Brown, Janet (Bradley), 1935 (Box 13, Folder 376)
  Correspondence with Janet Brown of Indianapolis, IN. Ms. Brown worked for Foster Hall, mounting photographs and negatives. She continued to do this work after the Collection moved to Pittsburgh.
- Brown, M.S., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 377)
  Correspondence with M.S. Brown of Spencer, IN. Organizer of a tour of Foster Hall for the Women's Club of Spencer.
- Brown, Mrs. Sedley, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 378)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Sedley Brown of Danbury, CT. Mrs. Brown married the nephew of SCF. She was one of the recipients of duplicates from the Collection.
- Brown University, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 379)
  Correspondence with Brown University in Providence, RI. Brown had a large collection of early American Music and exchanged photocopies of rare material with the Hall.
- Brown, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 380)
  Various correspondence with surname of "Brown".
- BU, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 381)
  Correspondence with Buffalo Forge Co.; Charles Burnham; Buck Creek Consolidated School; Robert E. Burke; Bond Byrd; Carl Busch; Bucknell University; Rosa Adam Burgess; Butler University; Buffalo Public Library; H.A. Burney; Lucile Burton; S.J. Bufkin; Allegra Parker Bufkin; Rev. D.C. Burnite; Henry Burkan; Admiral Richard Bird; Mortimer Bye; W.G. Burhans; KGIR Butte; WCAX Burlington; WEBR Buffalo; Burlington Daily News; Buffalo Grosvenor Library; University of Buffalo; A.E. Byrne; Mary Butkus; Buckeye Books; Gene Buck; Buckley, Dement & Co.; Wm. Marshall Bullitt; Buena Vista School; Bucknell University; Henry Butterfield
- Bundy, Annie M.P., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 382)
  Correspondence with Annie Bundy of Topeka, KS. A very persistent lady who tried repeatedly to get donations for a new music library in Topeka.
- Burdette, E. Marie, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 383)
  Correspondence with Marie Burdette of Winfield, KS, a loquacious visitor to the Hall.
- Burford Printing Co., Wm. B., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 384)
  Correspondence with William B. Burford Printing Company of Indianapolis, IN. This company did miscellaneous printing jobs for the Hall, such as invitations and Souvenir booklets.
- Butler, Amos W., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 385)
  Correspondence with Amos W. Butler of Indianapolis, IN. Correspondent who frequently pointed out printed references to Foster and his songs.
- BRO BRU BRY, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 386)
  Correspondence with Herbert Bruce Brougham; F.W. Brunkhorst; Brooklyn; Mary Brunnenmiller; Howard C. Bronson; Brookline; Brunswick, ME; Brooklyn Children's Museum; Margaret Brucker; Harry Bruning; Raymond Brummel; Robert Lee Brokenburr; Jane M. Brownell; WHN Brooklyn; South Dakota State College Brookings; KWWG Brownsville; WLTH Brooklyn; WCNW Brooklyn; Robert G. Brooke; Brooklyn College Library
- CAA CAP, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 387)
  Correspondence with H.A. Campbell; J.L. Cadick; Frank Caputo; Elizabeth Camburn; Mill College California; Radcliffe College Cambridge; Cairo Public Library; Culver Stockton College Library Canton MO; University of California; Harry Campbell; Raymond CaCa; Cable Piano Company; Calvin Campbell; Guy Campbell; Alta May Calkins; Wallace Cain; Keith Canan; A.P. Campbell; J. Campbell Cantrill; Cape Girardeau
- Callahan, Lorena, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 388)
  Correspondence with Lorena Callahan of Louisville, KY Not a dealer, but as a life-long resident of Louisville she was acquainted with many of the old families there, and obtained sheet music from them. Her letters are like full-length novels and she sounds quite mad. Over the years she developed a crush on Lilly and continued to write even after her flurry of sales dwindled away. The file for 1933 contains some interesting gossip about Col. La Bree. Mrs. Lott insinuates he stole a good deal of sheet music and other items from the MOKH museum. When Lilly remarried in 1935, Mrs. Lott turned her affections to Mr. Hodges.
- Capital Book Shop, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 389)
  Correspondence with the Capital Book shop of Hollywood, CA, a dealer in rare books. The owner makes some interesting comments about The Collector's Journal.
- CAR CAZ CE, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 390)
  Correspondence with Alice Caron; Mary A. Carbin; Carmel Public Schools; H.O. Carciofini; Carcy's Melody Boys The Kings of Rhythm; Andrew Malcolm Graham Casentini Esq.; Jefferson School Centralia; Kenneth Carpenter; V.J. Cariani; Donald Carpp; Central Press Clipping Service; Muriel Cashell; Caxton Book Shop Inc.; Herman Carter; Pearl Carle; Tudor Carre; Violet Carter; H.J. Certani; Helen L. Carrell; KDFN Casper; Cass County Historical Society; Gertrude Carpenter; Dr. F. de Carvalho; Carmi Public Library; Century Paper Company; Arthur B. Carlson; H.B. Carlisle
- Caslon Press, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 391)
  Correspondence with Caslon Press of Hollywood CA, another dealer.
- Certain, Mrs. Henry, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 392)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Henry Certain of Huntsville, AL. From 1931 on Mrs. Certain was one of the main suppliers of sheet music to Foster Hall. Her prices were always reasonable, and her material in good condition. Lilly so respected her business-like attitude and high standards that she was one of his personal guests at the dedication ceremonies in Pittsburgh.
- Chaney, E. Fred, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 393)
  Correspondence with E. Fred Cheney of Philadelphia, PA, a dealer who got into the game too late (as the Collection was ending completion). He offered many items but nothing of great value or interest.
- CH, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 394)
  Correspondence with Howard Chandler Christy; Chickasha Public School; K.K. Chen; Cecelia Charles; University of Chattanooga; Charlotte Public Library; Charleston Public Library; Mary L. Chishola; Rev. Thaddeus Cheatham; WCSC Charleston; WBT Charlotte; WEHC Charlottesville; Cheer Broadcasters; S.A. Chalfant; F. Christopher; Mary Chitwood
- Chicago, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 395)
  Letters from librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications
- Christopher, F., 1935 (Box 13, Folder 396)
  Correspondence with F. Christopher of South Orange, NJ. Christopher was a dealer, one of the first and most consistent suppliers of sheet music.
- CI CL, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 397)
  Correspondence with H.F. Clippinger; Cicero Public Schools; Clinton City Schools; J.L. Clough; KICA Clovis NM; J.L. Clough; Circleville High Street School; John R. Clements; Ruth Coleman; Virginia Clemson; Clarksdale Carnegie Public Library; Clearwater Public Library; L.S. Clark; J.M. Clayland; Sister M. Clotilde; Harry Clark; H.F. Clippinger; G.H.A. Clowes; Jessie M. Cleland; Marvine and Leslie Clark; Sarah Clarke; Claremont College Library; Hamilton College Library Clinton NY; Clark Consolidated School; A.B. Closson; Donald S. Clark; Durea Clevenger; Lucille Canon; Clinton Realty Company; Clinton Music Club
- Cincinnati Public Schools, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 398)
  Correspondence with Cincinnati Public Schools. All correspondence concerns the school songbooks published and distributed by Foster Hall.
- Cincinnati, University of, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 399)
  Correspondence with the University of Cincinnati. Early in 1935 Lilly offered to supply the University with a large Collection of Fosteriana. The University eagerly accepted. As well, Raymond Walters, President of the University and a Foster fan and Scholar, wrote a pamphlet entitled Youth's Golden Gleam and turned to Lilly for the money to publish it. Lilly subsidized publication through Princeton University Press.
- Cincinnati, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 400)
  Correspondence with librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations in Cincinnati, OH, thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications
- Clark, Florence, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 401)
  Correspondence with Florence Clark of Detroit, MI, a singer of American song who contacted the Hall after meeting Jessie Rose.
- Cleveland, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 402)
  Letters from librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations in Cleveland thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications
- COA COL COM, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 403)
  Correspondence with Edward Coffin; Colgate University Library; J. Winston Coleman; Virginia Combs; Louisa Coffin; Columbia High School; Theodore Collins; Richard Collins; Dr. Sidney Cohen; Colorado State Penitentiary; Alda Coito; Mary Collier; Colfax Library Trustees; S.M. Coleman; Sarah Collins; Robert Coates; Stuart Mosby Coleman; Columbia Broadcasting System; Columbia Phonograph Company; Arthur Cole; Colophon; Alfred Cobley; BElva Cochran
- Columbus, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 404)
  Letters from librarians, school teachers, children and radio stations in Columbus thanking Lilly for various Foster Hall Publications.
- CON COO COP COZ, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 405)
  Correspondence with Katherine Copley; David Costelo; M.W. Cox; R.M. Cone; Connecticut State Library; Cornell University Library; Connellsville Carnegie Free Library; Gerald Coventry; Dorothy Cookson; Ileen Copeland; Daisy Corbin; Albert Cox; Florence May Cox; C.G. Conn Ltd; Mary Corsini; J.R. Cordell; Rev. Francis Cox; D.H. Cotter; Beatrice Conn; Dr. Stanley Coulter; Hattie Carey; Country Research Club; Lindsay Carey; Guy Corliss; A.D. Coolbaugh; Walt Constantine; George Cottman; W.R. Conrad; Connersville Senior High School; Werner Conrad; Muriel Conger; Connecticut College; Public Library of Concord; Helen Condell
- Conn, Luella, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 406)
  Correspondence with Luella Conn of Dayton, OH. With Lilly supplying the funding, Mrs. Conn directed the recording of each of Foster's tunes on the Gennett record label. These Foster Hall Recordings were not for public sale; they were solely for use by the Hall. Recording was completed in 1936. Mrs. Conn was responsible for identifying that several of Foster's tunes consisted of different words set to the same air.
- Copley, Katharine, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 407)
  Correspondence with Katharine Copley of Washington, DC. Mrs. Copley was the daughter of W.R. Whittlesey and she also acted as his assistant in the research done at the Library of Congress for Foster Hall. After her father's death in 1936 she continued to work for the Hall on a part-time basis.
- Cooper, Montgomery, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 408)
  Correspondence with Montgomery Cooper of Memphis, TN, a rare book dealer.
- Cosmopolitan Book Mart, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 409)
  Correspondence with Cosmopolitan Book Mart of Chicago, IL, a rare book dealer
- CR CU CY, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 410)
  Correspondence with Cunard White Star Line; Crescent Paper Company; Richard Crooks; Harry Culbertson Inc; Crooksville Schools; J.W. Crumbaugh; Crookston Carnegie Public Library; Crescent City Women's Club; Cuba Public Schools; W.B. Cragon; Henrietta Crossman; A.L. Crabb; Ann Criswell; Mary Eloise Curl; F.R. Crandall; Dorothy Crown; Rosalind Cragun; Clifford V. Cross; Anita Crist; Clifford Cross; Jefferson Rural School Crestline; Glenna Crist; Kenneth Crawford; W.W. Creamer; Mary Alice Craft; Crawfordsville Church; W.A. Cunningham; Thomas Y. Crowell Company; Crawford Book Shop; Anna C. Crane; Association Broadcasting Company Cumberland MD; Culture Club; Drusilla Cravens; Cravenhurst; Evelyn Craig; Dr. Charles Crampton; Crofton Public School
- DA, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 411)